(Leonard:)- Just give us a few minutes.
- I'm running really late.
(Sheldon:)Then I have a simple solution.
(Sheldon:)Go up to the roof, hop over
to the next building... There's a gap.
(Sheldon:)Don't look down if you're subject
to vertigo... and use their stairwell.
- You're joking, right?
- Oh, I never joke when it comes to vertigo.
(Penny:)Damn. Okay, I'll just take the roof.
(Leonard:)If you wait for us
to set up the time machine...
(Leonard:)...I can drop you off at work yesterday.
Time-travel joke. It's not... Never mind.
(Sheldon:)For what it's worth,
I thought it was humorous.
[CHORTLES]
(Leonard:)Let's just do this.
- You guys ready to push?
RAJESH: In a minute.
(Raj:)Howard stepped outside to throw up.
(Sheldon:)I don't know what you were worried about.
I think it really works in the room.
(Leonard:)Yeah. It is by far the coolest thing
I have ever owned.
(Sheldon:)The exact time machine
that carried actor Rod Taylor...